

+48 696 912 106

• Wagowa 9/24 41-215 Sosnowiec

- github.com/sachedcrew
- · sachedcrew.github.io
- linkedin.com/in/sebastianploszaj

### About me

Creating websites became a path for me to realize my creativity already in high school. I was very passionate about the eHogwart browser game I designed. After graduating from high school, I chose to develop my humanistic interests – history, philosophy and psychology, where I could also use my ability to think analytically. For a year now, my goal has been to reindustry and develop in .NET technology. In private, my hobbies are music and sports.

### Skills

- C#
- HTML
- SQL
- CSS
- PHP
- JavaScript

### Frameworks

- ASP.NET
- Vue.js
- Laravel
- React
- Bootstrap

### Languages

- English B1
- German B1
- Polish Native

# Sebastian Płoszaj

.NET Developer

## Experience

PHP Developer (2015 - 2018)

- design and development of eHogwart.pl browser game (until 2016), peak period
  about 16,000. registered users
- creating components for websites in PHP, MySQL, JavaScript, HTML, CSS

.NET Developer (2022 - Present)

• creating web applications based on ASP.NET Core

### Education

University of Economics, Katowice, Poland Computer Science (2022 – Present)

- speciality: Algorithmics and programming
- the main direction of development is programming in C# and learning about relational databases

University of Silesia, Katowice, Poland History (2017 – 2020)

• graduated with a bachelor's degree

# Projects

### SkillStore E-commerce

ASP.NET, Bootsrap

- Admin Dashboard (Blazor)
- Razor Pages
- Registration & Login (Identity)
- Stripe Payments

e H o g w a r t Browser Game

PHP, MySQL, JavaScript, HTML, CSS

In the game, the user played the role of one of the Hogwarts students, where he could develop his skills, collect items, compete with other users

More information: mmorpg.com.pl/games/eHogwart